{
    "subject": "resource/Arnold_Schwarzenegger",
    "predicate": "ontology/spouse",
    "object": "resource/Maria_Shriver",
    "human_readable": "Arnold Schwarzenegger was married to Maria Shriver.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9795403480529785,
            "question": "When did Arnold Schwarzenegger and Maria Shriver get married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9539908766746521,
            "question": "What year was the marriage between Arnold Schwarzenegger and Maria Shriver finalized?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9303745031356812,
            "question": "To whom was Arnold Schwarzenegger married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8929576277732849,
            "question": "Who was married to Maria Shriver?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8779036998748779,
            "question": "Name a famous person who was married to Maria Shriver."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8477647304534912,
            "question": "Was Arnold Schwarzenegger ever married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7691646218299866,
            "question": "Are Arnold Schwarzenegger and Maria Shriver still together?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.750819206237793,
            "question": "Was Arnold Schwarzenegger's marriage successful?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6950550079345703,
            "question": "What is the name of Arnold Schwarzenegger's former wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.556172788143158,
            "question": "Who is Maria Shriver?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arnold Schwarzenegger was married to Maria Shriver.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7996_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Arnold Schwarzenegger's former wife?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7996_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Arnold Schwarzenegger's marriage successful?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7996_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Arnold Schwarzenegger and Maria Shriver still together?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7996_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7996_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7996_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7996_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7996_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7996_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7996_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7996_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7996_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7996_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7996_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query \"Arnold Schwarzenegger was married to Maria Shriver\":\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. Multiple documents mention that Arnold Schwarzenegger and Maria Shriver were married (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7996/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt) and that they eventually got divorced, but the fact that they were married is confirmed by multiple sources."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Arnold Schwarzenegger and Maria Shriver were indeed married. Multiple sources mention their marriage, including details such as the date of their marriage (April 26, 1986), the duration of their relationship (25 years), and its eventual end through divorce in 2011 due to infidelity on Schwarzenegger's part."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}